To summarize our discussion of dynamic dispatch, the body of the method is
总结一下我们对动态调度的讨论，该方法的主体是
invoked with, within environment e. That has definitions for the formal arguments
使用调用，在环境e.中调用，该环境具有形式参数的定义
and the attributes of the self object and a store that's just like color store
以及Self对象的属性和类似于色彩商店的商店
except that it also has the actual arguments bound to the locations allocated
除了它还将实际参数绑定到分配的位置之外
for the formal parameters. Notice in the rules that the notion of a frame or
用于形式参数。请注意，在规则中，框架或
activation records is implicit. We don't actually build a data structure. That
激活记录是隐式的。我们实际上并不构建数据结构。那
contains you know, all of the values all of the arguments and the, the return
包含所有的值，所有的参数和返回
address and all that stuff together. That information is not gathered together in
地址和所有这些东西在一起。这些信息不是集中在一起的
one place, it's a little more abstract. We don't actually have to say you know,
有一个地方，它有点抽象。我们实际上不需要说你知道，
whether things are allocated on the stack or on the heat and that's a good feature.
无论物品是堆叠分配的还是热分配的，这都是一个很好的特性。
That allows us to have, potentially have a range of implementations like all
这使得我们有，潜在地有一系列的实现，就像所有的
implement the semantics correctly. Now, we didn't do the semantics on the semantics
正确实现语义。现在，我们没有在语义上做语义
dispatch but it's extremely similar. The only difference is in how the class that
快递，但非常相似。唯一的不同之处在于班级如何
we are going to be dispatching to is looked up so in the stack dispatch you
我们将调度到IS进行查找，因此在堆栈中为您调度
might be able to you know, you can nam e the class that you want to dispatch to
也许能够让您知道，您可以命名要分派到的类
this one extra line to the side where the class is being dispatched to in the formal
这一行是在正式的类被分派到的一侧
rule and you can look in the manual to see how that works. So it's worth pointing out
规则，您可以在手册中查看它是如何工作的。所以值得指出的是
that while the operation of rules are very detailed, they intentionally omit some
虽然规则的操作非常详细，但他们故意省略了一些
cases that you might think they should cover so let's take a look at our dispatch
您可能认为他们应该涵盖的情况，所以让我们看看我们的发货
example again. So here notice that we look up the class of v0. So v0 is an object and
再举一个例子。请注意，我们在这里查找的是V0的类。所以V0是一个物体，
we checked what is class tag is and then we look up in that class, the name of the
我们检查了什么是类标记，然后在那个类中查找
method that we're dispatching to and we get out a definition of the method or not
方法，然后我们得到该方法的定义或不定义
the definition of the method that we can write the rest of the rule. Now what would
方法的定义，那就是我们可以写睡觉的规则。现在有什么会
happen If there was no such method f in the class x, I mean this, this rule just
如果在类x中没有这样的方法f就会发生，我是说这个，这个规则
assumes that method is in fact to define the class x, And the rule doesn't say
假设该方法实际上是定义类x，并且规则没有说明
anything about what to do if it turns out that this class x doesn't have any method
如果发现这个类x没有任何方法，该怎么办
f? Well, that actually can't happen. So, type-checking has already guaranteed That
F？嗯，那实际上是不可能的。因此，类型检查已经保证了
when we go to look up method as in class x it will exist. That was one of the points
当我们在类x中查找方法时，它将存在。这是其中一点
with the type checking rules was that no dynamic dispatch could ever dispatch to a
类型检查规则的一个特点是，任何动态分派都不能分派到
method that wasn't defined. And so the fact that the time checking is already
未定义的方法。所以事实上时间检查已经是
been done, it will allows us to meet some cases. So there's some checks that we
已经完成了，这将使我们能够遇到一些情况。所以我们有一些支票
don't have to do because we know that, that system has already effectively done
不需要这样做，因为我们知道，这个系统已经有效地做到了
that And the rules would only be more complicated if we didn't have type
如果我们没有类型，那么规则只会更加复杂
checking and we needed to actually say what would happen you know, all of the
正在检查，我们需要实际说出会发生什么，你知道，所有的
cases where type checking will work where things were not typed correct. Now there
类型检查将起作用的情况下，输入的内容不正确。现在就在那里
are some run time errors that the type checker doesn't prevent however and in
是否存在一些类型检查器无法阻止的运行时错误
cool there are four. One is to dispatch the void. Divisions by zero you can have a
太好了，一共有四个。其一是派遣空位。除以零，你可以得到一个
sub-screen in that excess out of range or you could run out of memory. You could try
子屏幕中超出范围，否则可能会耗尽内存。你可以试试
allocating new objects that do not have enough space for that. And in such cases,
分配空间不足的新对象。在这种情况下，
the execution has to aboard gracefully an d that means with an error message and not
执行必须优雅地执行，这意味着带有错误消息，而不是
just with a segmentation fault or some other kind of hard crash and in the manual
只是出现了分段故障或其他类型的硬崩溃，并且在手册中
there some guidelines as to what a correct co-implementation should do in this four
关于正确的联合实现应该在这四个方面做些什么，有一些指导方针
situations. To summarize the material in the last couple of videos the operational
情况。总结最后几个视频中的内容
semantic rules are really very precised and detail. If you understand them then
语义规则确实非常精确和详细。如果你能听懂他们的话
you really understand how to implement a correct cool compiler. So the rules are
您真正了解了如何实现一个正确的酷编译器。所以规则是
complete enough and give you enough detail that it really can't go wrong if you just
足够完整，给你足够的细节，如果你只是
implement what the rules tell you to do. So you need to read the rules very
执行规则告诉你要做的事情。所以你需要非常仔细地阅读规则
carefully And I'll emphasize that because there's actually quite a lot going on in
小心，我会强调这一点，因为实际上有相当多的事情发生在
the rules. They're written in a certain way and you know, to, to achieve a certain
这是规则。它们是以某种方式写的，你知道，为了达到某种目的
effect and I pointed out a couple of subtle things in the rules and so you
效果，我指出了规则中的几个微妙之处，所以你
know, you really have to actually study the rules in order to internalize what
要知道，你真的必须真正研究规则，才能将什么内在化
they mean and be able to. Implement them correctly. It's also a great way
他们的意思是而且能够做到。正确实施它们。这也是一种很好的方式
understanding these rules and details was actually a great way to learn quite a bit
理解这些规则和细节实际上是一个很好的学习方法
of the, the kind of formal thinking that goes in to the design of programming
程序设计中的一种形式思维
languages and what it means for a programming language to have a semantics
语言以及编程语言具有语义的含义
and for implementation of something to be correct. Now having settled that, I should
为了让某些事情的实施是正确的。现在解决了这个问题，我应该
say that most languages do not have a well specified operational semantics. There are
假设大多数语言没有明确指定的操作语义。确实有
some there are some substantial languages and fairly realistic languages that do
有些语言和相当现实的语言可以做到这一点
have a formal semantics but most of the language is that you're familiar with do
有一个正式的语义，但是大部分的语言都是你熟悉的
not. Finally just a comment you know when portability is important, when you really
不。最后只是一个评论，你知道什么时候可移植性很重要，什么时候你真的
want software that you write behave the exactly the same in different environments
希望您编写的软件在不同环境中的行为完全相同
so you know if I take the same program and I move it to a different machine or a
所以你知道，如果我把相同的程序移到不同的机器上，或者
different operating system and I still want to kind of guarantee that this offer
不同的操作系统，我仍然想要某种程度上保证这个服务
will behave as it as it you know the same on both machine or the old environment and
将按照您所知道的在两台计算机或旧环境上相同的方式运行，并且
the new environment then I really need some independent defin ition of what it
新的环境，我真的需要一些独立的定义
means what the behavior of these programs should be. And that's where a formal
意味着这些程序的行为应该是什么。这就是一个正式的
semantics becomes a really critical.
语义学变得非常关键。